us-immigration.com 2014-04-15

# Privacy Notice

**_PRIVACY POLICY_**

American Immigration Center Inc. ("AIC"), a Florida corporation, and its website presently located at www.us-immigration.com ("Website"), offer do-it-yourself U.S. immigration products that are designed to provide customers with general information pertaining to specific U.S. immigration forms, applications and procedures. 

AIC has created this Privacy Policy to explain the type of information gathered from a user's (a "User,""you" or "your") visit to and use of its Website. 

**_Non-Personal Information_**

Certain non-personal information, including but not limited to the type of browser being used, its operating system and the User's IP address, may be automatically recorded by the standard operation of the Website's internet servers. This information can be used to help diagnose server problems, administer the Website and generally enhance the User's online experience. 

**_Personal Identifiable Information_**

Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") is not automatically collected from the User's visit to the Website, as a general policy. PII includes, without limitation: (i) contact data (such as a User's first and last name, physical street address, city, state, zip code, phone number and email address), (ii) financial data (such as a User's credit card number, expiration date, and verification code), (iii) demographic data (such as a User's zip code and gender), and (iv) other legal data (such as a User's social security number and other sensitive information necessary to complete and generate the proper documents). 

However, AIC will collect and use PII about you to respond to your request for products or services offered through the Website. AIC will also collect this information in order to notify you about products, services, and other opportunities we think will be of interest to you. The information AIC collects may be from, (a) information provided by you when registering for a form service or product offered through the Website, for example, you will be required to submit personal information such as your name, address, email, and date of birth to verify your identity prior to establishing your account; (b) billing information, such as a credit card number, which is required to process the payment for the products or services you order from us; (c) other information we collect, such as the city of your birth and your mother's maiden name, which is used to verify your identity in the event you forget your login information required for our online products or services; (d) information you provide AIC in response to our communications, for example, AIC may request that you provide your e-mail address so that we may send you notifications, alerts, special offers and newsletters; and/or (e) information that you provide to AIC through customer service correspondence and general feedback. 

We will also collect certain information arising out of your use of the Website, or augment the data we collect with other information from other online or offline sources. AIC reserves the right to collect information about you and store it in connection with other online or offline information we may possess or obtain about you. 

Please be advised that certain PII becomes public record upon the filing of certain documents with the appropriate government agency or court. Additionally, AIC may disclose a User's information in special cases when AIC has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with AIC's rights or property, another User or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. However AIC will not sell, lease or otherwise make available to any person or entity not authorized by or associated with AIC your PII. 

**_Free Qualifying Quiz_**

Information you provide during the Free Qualifying Quiz will not be stored anywhere or distributed to any third party. It will only be used to determine whether or not you meet the requirements set forth by the USCIS to apply for the intended application. 

**_Opt-Out_**

If you do not wish to receive mailings regarding new offers, products or services offered by AIC, our partners or our affiliates, you may opt out by emailing a request to Customer Service at any time at cs@us-immigration.com. 

**_Sharing of Information_**

AIC may share information about you with affiliated and non-affiliated third parties when you visit the Website or register for or purchase one of our products or services. This includes, with out limitation, the following: (a) Vendors - We sometimes disclose the information we collect to companies that operate various services for us, such as marketing, distribution, advertising, or certain product functionalities; (b) Transferability of Information - In the event we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your PII and any information you provide to us will likely be among the assets transferred; (c) As Permitted by Law - AIC may share your non-public PII and PII with non-affiliated third parties as permitted by law; and (d) Bankruptcy - if we file for bankruptcy, reorganization, insolvency, if a receiver is appointed over us, or an assignment for the benefit of creditors, or other applicable creditors rights laws, we may not be able to control how your PII is treated or used. 

AIC may disclose the information that we collect to our affiliated companies from time to time for marketing purposes and to enhance our products or services to better suit your needs. When identifying methods of improving our products or services, or if we think a product or service may be of interest to you, we may extend select special offers of goods or services to you. If you would like to opt-out of receiving these offers, please refer to the "Opt-Out," section above. 

The Website may contain links for other offers, products and/or services that we feel you may have an interest in, however we urge you to review such websites' respective privacy policies. AIC is deeply committed to a User's right to privacy. However, please note that this Website's Privacy Policy only applies to the Website and not to any other websites that a User may access from the Website, each of which may have privacy policies that are materially different from this Privacy Policy. We encourage each User to be aware when he or she leaves the Website and to read the privacy policies of each and every other website. We are not responsible or liable in connection with your use of any other website. 

**_Tracking Cookies_**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on a User's hard drive that contains information about the User and that is used for record keeping purposes. Cookies enable AIC to track and target the interests of a User to enhance his or her experience on the Website. We may set and access cookies on your computer to provide you with customized content and to assist in providing the products that you have requested. 

We also work with companies who provide services to maintain the Website and enable those service providers the right to use cookies on our website. Most cookies automatically delete themselves from your hard drive after each session. 

Like many other websites, AIC may automatically track information based upon your behavior on the Website. AIC may combine information that we obtain through the use of cookies with PII, other aggregate or anonymous data, including a unique identification we may assign you. As described above, AIC and third parties authorized by AIC may use this information to better understand, protect and provide products to you. The information may include browser type, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, IP address, and number of clicks, all used to analyze trends, administer the Website, track a User's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

Most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies; however, a User can reset his or her web browser to reject all cookies. If a User rejects the cookie, he or she may still use the Website, although some areas of the Website may have limited access. 

**_Minors_**

You must be at least 18 years of age or the legal age to form a binding contract in your jurisdiction if that age is greater than 18 years of age in order to use the Website and/or its products and/or services. The Website is not intended for use by persons under the age of 18. AIC does not knowingly solicit personal information from such persons or send them requests for non-public personal information. If you are under the age of 18, you must not sending us any personal information or use our products or services. 

**_Information Security_**

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards designed to protect your nonpublic personal information. We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you or your children (if applicable) to our employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you, as well as to authorized third parties (as stated above). AIC protects your information over the internet by using a secure web server, which allows web browser programs (Netscape or Microsoft Internet Explorer) to interact with our web server via an encrypted session. AIC employs a Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) connection that provides an encrypted connection between your computer and AIC. The 128 bit encrypted connection scrambles ordinary text or data into cyphertext to safeguard sensitive information during its journey across the internet. The information is decrypted, or put back into a readable format, when it reaches its intended destination. Depending on which browser you use, you will know you are in secured area by "https" or a lock appearing in the lower right hand corner of your browser window. When you visit the Website, you may move in and out of secured areas. Anytime that you are on a page ordering products or services, or viewing your personal credit report, you will be in a secured area. Notwithstanding the forgoing, we will have no liability to a User or to any third party arising out of any loss, misuse, destruction, or alteration of a User's information. 

**_User's Acceptance & Notification of Changes_**

By using the Website, the User signifies his or her acceptance of all terms set forth in AIC's Privacy Policy. If the User does not agree to accept all or any portion of such terms, then the User is respectfully asked not to use the Website. AIC reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time, so Users are encouraged to review this Privacy Policy from time to time. A User's continued use of the Website following the posting of such modifications, alterations or updates will signify the User's acceptance thereof. 

If at any point AIC decides to use PII in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, AIC will notify the Users by way of email. Each User will have a choice whether or not we use his or her information in this different manner. If AIC decides to change its Privacy Policy, AIC will post those changes on the Website so that the Users are always aware of what information AIC collects, how such information is used and under what circumstances, if any, such information is disclosed. 

_Last Updated: December 18, 2012_
